<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Look of Introspection</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on A Look of Introspection</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hbrinj.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SwiftUI Super Powered - ViewBuilders</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/swiftui-viewbuilders/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/swiftui-viewbuilders/</guid><description>The Problem How can a View be augmented with new properties without having a knock on effect, changing all other uses of said view?
The solution ViewBuilders, a parameter attribute which allows you to supplement an existing view by capturing it as a view producing closure. The example we&amp;rsquo;ll work with today is the concept of turning an existing view, used to represent a row in a List view, into a view which displays where it has been selected.</description></item><item><title>SwiftUI Super Powered</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/swiftuipowered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/swiftuipowered/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a project which is going to be focusing on using SwiftUI in its entirety. The project is pretty straight forward in that there are numerous applications on the app store that provide a solution to this problem. It is a resource tracker that generates a QR code which can be used to identify one or more assets. Resources can also be grouped into boxes. The app is meant to do one thing and do it well.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Hugo Site Using GitHub Actions</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/github-actions-and-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/github-actions-and-hugo/</guid><description>GitHub Actions are a suite of user and GitHub created abilities which allow you to declare a pipeline straight in GitHub. They permit your project to build and deploy different components without the need for spinning up your own CI/CD infrastructure. GitHub Actions run using docker containers which allow you to bake in any required dependencies.
A bundle of actions is called a workflow on GitHub and it exists within your repo under .</description></item><item><title>Integrating Namecheap and GitHub Pages</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/namecheap-githubpages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/namecheap-githubpages/</guid><description>Namecheap as the name suggests provides cheap names, in particular they provide domain names like the one this website is using. This site may or may not be on GitHub anymore when you the readers are reading this, but in its inception I went for the quick and dirty route and utilised GitHub Pages.
To point your domain to your GitHub Pages domain, follow this Namecheap domain with GitHub pages tutorial.</description></item><item><title>Note: this is unsafe</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/thisisunsafes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/thisisunsafes/</guid><description>NOTE: Don&amp;rsquo;t do this if you are not sure about the validity and trustworthiness of the website you are visiting.
thisisunsafe is all you need to bypass NET::ERR_CERT_INVALID exceptions when you come across them in Chrome. Click anywhere on the page and enter that key phrase, but do so at your own risk.</description></item><item><title>Something New Stirs</title><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/some-new-stirs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/posts/some-new-stirs/</guid><description>This is the first post on this website! everything needs a beginning.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/about/</guid><description>WIP</description></item><item><title/><link>https://hbrinj.github.io/showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hbrinj.github.io/showcase/</guid><description>WIP</description></item></channel></rss>